[
    {"question": "あ", "answer": "a"},
    {"question": "い", "answer": "i"},
    {"question": "う", "answer": "u"},
    {"question": "え", "answer": "e"},
    {"question": "お", "answer": "o"},
    {"question": "か", "answer": "ka"},
    {"question": "き", "answer": "ki"},
    {"question": "く", "answer": "ku"},
    {"question": "け", "answer": "ke"},
    {"question": "こ", "answer": "ko"},
    {"question": "さ", "answer": "sa"},
    {"question": "し", "answer": "shi"},
    {"question": "す", "answer": "su"},
    {"question": "せ", "answer": "se"},
    {"question": "そ", "answer": "so"},
    {"question": "た", "answer": "ta"},
    {"question": "ち", "answer": "chi"},
    {"question": "つ", "answer": "tsu"},
    {"question": "て", "answer": "te"},
    {"question": "と", "answer": "to"},
    {"question": "な", "answer": "na"},
    {"question": "に", "answer": "ni"},
    {"question": "ぬ", "answer": "nu"},
    {"question": "ね", "answer": "ne"},
    {"question": "の", "answer": "no"},
    {"question": "は", "answer": "ha"},
    {"question": "ひ", "answer": "hi"},
    {"question": "ふ", "answer": "fu"},
    {"question": "へ", "answer": "he"},
    {"question": "ほ", "answer": "ho"},
    {"question": "ま", "answer": "ma"},
    {"question": "み", "answer": "mi"},
    {"question": "む", "answer": "mu"},
    {"question": "め", "answer": "me"},
    {"question": "も", "answer": "mo"},
    {"question": "や", "answer": "ya"},
    {"question": "ゆ", "answer": "yu"},
    {"question": "よ", "answer": "yo"},
    {"question": "ら", "answer": "ra"},
    {"question": "り", "answer": "ri"},
    {"question": "る", "answer": "ru"},
    {"question": "れ", "answer": "re"},
    {"question": "ろ", "answer": "ro"},
    {"question": "わ", "answer": "wa"},
    {"question": "を", "answer": "wo"},
    {"question": "きゃ", "answer": "kya"},
    {"question": "きゅ", "answer": "kyu"},
    {"question": "きょ", "answer": "kyo"},
    {"question": "しゃ", "answer": "sha"},
    {"question": "しゅ", "answer": "shu"},
    {"question": "しょ", "answer": "sho"},
    {"question": "ちゃ", "answer": "cha"},
    {"question": "ちゅ", "answer": "chu"},
    {"question": "ちょ", "answer": "cho"},
    {"question": "にゃ", "answer": "nya"},
    {"question": "にゅ", "answer": "nyu"},
    {"question": "にょ", "answer": "nyo"},
    {"question": "ひゃ", "answer": "hya"},
    {"question": "ひゅ", "answer": "hyu"},
    {"question": "ひょ", "answer": "hyo"},
    {"question": "みゃ", "answer": "mya"},
    {"question": "みゅ", "answer": "myu"},
    {"question": "みょ", "answer": "myo"},
    {"question": "りゃ", "answer": "rya"},
    {"question": "りゅ", "answer": "ryu"},
    {"question": "りょ", "answer": "ryo"},
    {"question": "ぎゃ", "answer": "gya"},
    {"question": "ぎゅ", "answer": "gyu"},
    {"question": "ぎょ", "answer": "gyo"},
    {"question": "じゃ", "answer": "ja"},
    {"question": "じゅ", "answer": "ju"},
    {"question": "じょ", "answer": "jo"},
    {"question": "びゃ", "answer": "bya"},
    {"question": "びゅ", "answer": "byu"},
    {"question": "びょ", "answer": "byo"},
    {"question": "ぴゃ", "answer": "pya"},
    {"question": "ぴゅ", "answer": "pyu"},
    {"question": "ぴょ", "answer": "pyo"},
    {"question": "ぢゃ", "answer": "ja"},
    {"question": "ぢゅ", "answer": "ju"},
    {"question": "ぢょ", "answer": "jo"},
    {"question": "ん", "answer": "n"}
    ]